freestufftimes.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy - Free Stuff Times

Your privacy is very important to Freestufftimes. Accordingly, Freestufftimes has implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you, the user, of the information that Freestufftimes collects from you, how Freestufftimes collects this information, and what Freestufftimes’ does with it after it is collected. By using the Freestufftimes.com Web Site you are accepting the practices described in this policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact Freestufftimes at: webmaster@Freestufftimes.com

What Types of Information Does Freestufftimes.com Collect From Me?

Personal Information. For each visitor to the Site, the our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

Non-Personal Information. Freestufftimes also collects “non-personal” information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous web site you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your IP Address. This information (”Non-Personal Information”) cannot be easily used to personally identify you.

How Does Freestufftimes Use My Information?

Freestufftimes uses Personal Information and Non-Personal Information primarily to improve the content of Freestufftimes Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to Freestufftimes Web site, used by Freestufftimes to contact consumers for marketing purposes, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

When Will Freestufftimes Disclose My Information to Third Parties?

Generally speaking, Freestufftimes does not intentionally disclose your information to third parties without your consent. However, Freestufftimes reserves the right to do so because it is necessary to the operation and continued growth of Freestufftimes or to protect the rights of others. These instances are discussed below:

Disclosure to Successors. Freestufftimes may disclose your Personal Information to any successor-in-interest of Freestufftimes, such as a company that acquires Freestufftimes. In the event Freestufftimes goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or by a notice on the Freestufftimes Web Site of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Disclosure to Unaffiliated Third Parties. Freestufftimes may disclose your Personal Information to prevent an emergency, to protect or enforce our rights, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order). Freestufftimes may disclose your information to a third party that alleges that you have infringed their intellectual property rights. Similarly, if you allege that a user allegedly infringed on your intellectual property rights, Freestufftimes may disclose your information to that user.

Disclosure to Third-Party Service Providers. Freestufftimes may contract with various third parties who help Freestufftimes provide and maintain the Web Site.. Freestufftimes cannot guarantee that such third parties will not disclose your Personal Information. Additionally, please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online — for example, via message boards or chat — that information can be collected and used by people you don’t know. While Freestufftimes Forums strives to protect your personal information and privacy, Freestufftimes cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online; you make such disclosures at your own risk. However, if you violate the rules, Freestufftimes Forums reserves the right to disclose any and all user activity to the public, third parties and or law enforcement agencies. With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, Freestufftimes has relationships with other companies that allow other companies to place ads on the Freestufftimes Web Site. As a result of your visit to Freestufftimes site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

What About Cookies?

A cookie is a message that is sent to your computer from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. With respect to cookies: Freestufftimes does not set any cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Freestufftimes only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Does Freestufftimes.com Protect My Personal Information?

Whenever Freestufftimes obtains your Personal Information, Freestufftimes uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, Freestufftimes is not an insurer of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, Freestufftimes assumes no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond Freestufftimes reasonable control.

Web Site Content. The content that you store, post, or transmit on or through the Web Site, such as message board postings, your profile page, and images you upload to the Web Site, may be accessed by other users, including people that you do not know. Freestufftimes is not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your Personal Information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private.

Security

The security of your personal information is important to Freestufftimes.

Freestufftimes follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to Freestufftimes, both during transmission and once Freestufftimes receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Freestufftimes strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, Freestufftimes cannot guarantee its absolute security.

What About Children’s Privacy?

Under Thirteen. The Freestufftimes Services are only for users ages 13 and older. Accordingly, Freestufftimes will delete any information that Freestufftimes knows originates from a child under the age of 13.  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at webmaster *at* freestufftimes dot .com

At www.freestufftimes.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.freestufftimes.com and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.freestufftimes.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.freestufftimes.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.freestufftimes.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.freestufftimes.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Linkshare  
Amazon

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.freestufftimes.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.freestufftimes.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.freestufftimes.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
